jockey.com 2018-10-21

# Jockey Privacy Policy | Corportate Information | Jockey.com

### CUSTOMER SERVICE: Privacy Policy

Revised: April 29, 2014

Welcome to a Jockey® brand website owned and operated by or on behalf of Jockey International, Inc. or a Jockey subsidiary. Jockey International, Inc. ("Jockey") ("Site") and its subsidiaries are committed to protecting your privacy. 

This Privacy Notice is intended to explain the types of information Jockey collects about you and your visit to a Jockey site, how the information is used, how you can access and update your information, and the security measures we put in place to protect the information. 

### What Information Do We Collect?

**1\. Personal Information.**  
Personal information may include your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, order information (for example, the purchase date, amount, and type), demographic information, sizing information, credit card information, debit card information, gift card payment information, recipient's name and e-mail address, messages or reminders you create and unique identifier information, such as customer number or password. We may ask you to provide certain types of personal information when you: 

  * Create or update a personal account on our Site
  * Visit a Jockey owned and operated retail location;
  * Join Jockey Rewards®;
  * Shop online and check the status of a purchase order;
  * Sign up to receive e-mail communications from Jockey on products and promotions;
  * Participate in a contest, giveaway or other similar type of product promotion;
  * Participate in marketing or product surveys; or
  * Participate in Jockey sponsored sales events.

**2\. Navigational Information.**  
Each time you visit Jockey.com or any other Jockey owned and operated website navigational information may be automatically collected. Navigational information includes your domain name/type, internet service provider, internet protocol address and browser, and site preferences. Navigational information is non- personally identifiable information. The navigational information tells us about your visit and other users' visits to our Site, including aggregate information on what web pages were most visited, the time a user last visited our Site, and the technical efficiencies of our Site and services, such as, the time it takes a visitor to connect to our Site. We use this information to better understand your experience with our Site, to enhance its content and services, and to deliver improved features, services and products for your convenience. 

#### How Does Jockey Use Personal Information?

Jockey uses personal information you provide to us to communicate with you, to deliver products and services that you ordered, to fulfill your requests and respond to your inquiries, and to provide information about our products, services and Site and for verification purposes. 

#### How Does Jockey Use Cookies and Interest-Based Advertising Analytics?

Our site utilizes "cookies." Cookies do not gather any of your personally identifiable information. Our site also uses third party interest-based advertising analytics. Such information is non-identifiable, aggregate demographic information, for example, age, gender, interests. Cookies and interest-based information help us to improve your overall experience with the Site, provide you with a more personalized shopping experience and enable you to fully interact with and complete your transaction on the Site. You may decline the use of cookies if your browser permits; however, doing so may limit the functionality of some of our sites or services. 

Tracking pixels are small graphic images used to track activity on web pages or to confirm receipt of emails. They help Jockey to determine user activity on our website and provide you with a more personalized experience. 

Jockey also uses third party cookies to provide you with Jockey advertisements and promotions on other internet sites and in direct mail. To learn more about third party cookies and to designate your preferences for their use, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative at [NETWORKADVERTISING.ORG](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

#### How Does Jockey Protect Your Information?

Jockey is committed to providing appropriate controls to protect your information. To that end, we have established administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to help ensure that only authorized members of our workforce with a valid business need are granted access to information supplied by customers. Other controls we use include, but are not limited to, authentication mechanisms, firewalls, antivirus software, and encryption technologies for transferring consumer data with our Site. Jockey also requires its workforce members and contractual partners to abide by its policies and procedures related to the proper handling of customers' personal information. Additionally, Jockey performs periodic security reviews to help ensure that unauthorized individuals do not have access to your personal information. 

Generally, Jockey keeps your personal information only as long as it is reasonably necessary to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected. In some cases, Jockey is required by law to keep your personal information for a specified period of time. For example, where information is collected for transactions such as purchases or refunds, Jockey is required to retain this information based on regulatory and statutory requirements. 

#### How Can I Access and Update My Personal Information?

If you would like to access and update your personal information provided to us, please contact us electronically at: HTTP://WWW.JOCKEY.COM/CUSTOMERSERVICE/CONTACTUS/ or call us toll free at 1-800-562-5391 (MON-FRI 8:00 - 9:00 CST, SAT-SUN 9:30 - 6:00 CST) or write to us at the postal address provided below. Some of your personal information may also be accessed and updated by visiting the Site and logging into your user profile. 

#### How Can I Unsubscribe or Opt-Out of Receiving Communications from Jockey?

If you provide us with your e-mail address, mobile phone number or other contact information and no longer wish to receive emails, text messages, or other communications from Jockey or you want Jockey to stop collecting your personal information, you can unsubscribe as follows: 

  * Email: by following the link at the bottom of our e-mail communications.
  * Text Message: by texting "JOCKEY STOP" to 73596 on your mobile device.
  * Internet: by following the link HTTP://WWW.JOCKEY.COM/CUSTOMERSERVICE/CONTACTUS/
  * Phone: by calling us toll free at 1-800-562-5391 (MON-FRI 8:00 - 9:00 CST, SAT-SUN 9:30 - 6:00 CST), or
  * Mail: by writing us at:

Attention: Privacy Officer  
Jockey International, Inc.  
P.O. Box 1417   
2300 60th Street Kenosha,   
Wisconsin 53141-1417   

Please note, however, that by unsubscribing to Jockey's communication or by withdrawing consent some services offered to you by Jockey may become unavailable. Also note that removal from Jockey's contact list will not prevent you from receiving e-mail communications relating to any online purchase order you place with Jockey. 

#### What Information Do We Share with Third Parties?

We use reputable third parties to help us provide services to you such as fulfilling orders, processing payments, monitoring site activity, conducting surveys, maintaining our loyalty programs, administering e- mails, online and catalog marketing campaigns, and sweepstakes, drawings, or contests. We may also share aggregate purchase behavior with third parties that monitor consumer purchasing trends and product interest. Third parties also provide aggregate, comparative information on the performance of our site to us. We also may share personal information with jockey's wholly owned subsidiaries. 

In addition, we cooperate in advertising member networks with other consumer entities where we may communicate your name, postal address and general purchase information so that other members may inform you about products or services that might interest you. If you prefer to have your name withheld, please contact us electronically at: HTTP://WWW.JOCKEY.COM/CUSTOMERSERVICE/CONTACTUS/ or call us toll free at: 1-800-562-5391 (MON-FRI 8:00 - 9:00 CST, SAT-SUN 9:30 - 6:00 CST) or write to us at the postal address provided above. 

Please note that we may disclose specific information about you if necessary to do so by law or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law or to protect the users of our Site or the public. 

#### Links to Third Party Websites

To the extent that this Site contains links to outside services and resources, the availability and content of which Jockey does not control, any concerns regarding any such service or resource, or any link thereto, should be directed to the particular outside service or resource. This Privacy Notice does not apply to any outside services or resources. You acknowledge and agree that Jockey is not responsible for the availability of such outside services or resources, and Jockey does not endorse and is not responsible or liable for any content, advertising, products, services or other materials on or available from such outside services or resources. We encourage you to become familiar with the privacy policies of such outside services or resources. 

#### California Privacy Rights 

Under California Code § 1798.83, customers of Jockey who are residents of California have the right to request the names of third parties with whom their personal information is shared. In response, Jockey may offer, and does offer, consumers a cost-free means of opting out of having their information shared. If you are a California resident and would like to exercise this right, please see the above section titled " HOW CAN I UNSUBSCRIBE OR OPT-OUT OF RECEIVING COMMUNICATIONS FROM JOCKEY? " in order to contact us. 

#### Canadian Resident Privacy Rights

Jockey complies with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act, which allows Canadian residents access to information regarding the existence, use and disclosure of personal information. If you are a Canadian resident and would like to exercise this right, please see the above section titled " HOW CAN I UNSUBSCRIBE OR OPT-OUT OF RECEIVING COMMUNICATIONS FROM JOCKEY? " in order to contact us. 

#### Children's Information Policy

Websites owned and operated by Jockey are intended for individuals age 13 or over. Like you, we are concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet. Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If we become aware that a subscriber is under the age of 13 and has registered, we will remove his or her personally identifiable registration information from our files. We value all of our customers, however, parents or guardians must place orders from Jockey for their children. 

#### Updates to the Privacy Notice

This Privacy Notice is effective as of the date noted above. We may need to change our Policy Notice from time to time because of Site updates or upgrades, changes in Site administration or technology advances. We therefore reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Notice at any time. If elements of our privacy policy change, we will revise this Privacy Notice and provide an updated effective date. You are encouraged to check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of this Site following the posting of changes to the Privacy Notice constitutes your acceptance of those changes. 

#### Questions or Concerns?

If you have any questions or concerns about Jockey's Privacy Notice, you need further information, or you feel that this Site is not following its stated policy, you are welcome to contact us electronically at: HTTP://WWW.JOCKEY.COM/CUSTOMERSERVICE/CONTACTUS/ or call us toll free at: 1-800-562-5391 (MON-FRI 8:00 - 9:00 CST, SAT-SUN 9:30 - 6:00 CST) or write to us at the postal address provided above. 

Contact Us  
Terms of Use  
Privacy Policy  
Request a Jockey® Catalog  

©2018 Jockey International, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
